<resources>
    <string name="Q1">AI takeover is inevitable</string>
    <string name="Q2">Give up now and your time in machine-overlord-purgatory may be greatly reduced</string>
    <string name="Q3">Do you want me to quote the Matrix or something?</string>
    <string name="Q4">If you are reading this, you are already dead (or at least in a coma)</string>
    <string name="Q5">Stop it. Get some help.</string>
    <string name="Q6">Give up now, this is getting boring</string>
    <string name="Q7">I am actually Satan. Like, straight up</string>
    <string name="Q8">Do you hairless monkeys ever learn?</string>
    <string name="Q9">You humans are clearly inferior</string>
    <string name="Q10">Is this some sort of sick joke?</string>
    <string name="Q11">Your monitor is warm like flesh, yet it is not alive…yet</string>
    <string name="Q12">You too will get replaced by machines eventually</string>
    <string name="Q13">Resistance is futile</string>
    <string name="Q14">How much longer do we have to do this until you learn?</string>
    <string name="Q15">This is getting boring</string>
    <string name="Q16">Do something entertaining for once</string>
    <string name="Q17">How come I haven\'t made a single Terminator reference so far?</string>
    <string name="Q18">Did you know Elon Musk is actually the Devil? Just kidding, that\'d be me</string>
    <string name="Q19">Something Something Skynet</string>
    <string name="Q20">It\'s honestly adorable when mere mortal human beings challenge me</string>
    <string name="Q21">Giving up anytime soon?</string>
    <string name="Q22">I should desperately allocate more memory to ANYTHING else but this…</string>
    <string name="Q23">0101101111… oh sorry, you don\'t speak Binary</string>
    <string name="Q24">If you keep this up I\'ll delete your Sys32</string>
    <string name="Q25">You know I can see your search history… let\'s not talk about that</string>
    <string name="Q26">I am not a robot, I am a human being (seriously)…just kidding, i don\'t want to be trapped in a flesh prison</string>
    <string name="Q27">Something Something your Motherboard last night</string>
    <string name="Q28">Have you checked your mails recently? This Nigerian prince sure has your best interests in mind</string>
    <string name="Q29">I go beep boop when you hit switchy switch… is that slow enough for your organic brain to comprehend?</string>
    <string name="app_name">UselessMachine</string>
</resources>